Part 1 - polynomial_zeros.ipynb does not show up in the above commit because Git handles a merged result by comparing the previous commits used to obtain that result. Since the F commit already came from a parent commit that had removed polynomial_zeros.ipynb, it does not appear in the text comparison.

Part 2 - I decided to keep the test that uses the fractions module because it is less affected by precision loss that could result from using floating numbers such as decimals, which seems to be the method employed by the other test.

Part 3 - Frank's comment is referring to the fact that every time a change or combination is made in the report, every merge or rebase command requires resolving any text conflicts from different team members in the report.md file.

Part 4 - the tests passing depends on the commit with hash <0c218ed> which determines whether pytest can run the test files. By merging or rebasing part4 into main, this commit gets left behind at the root of the composite branch. This issue could be resolved by cherry-picking this commit and appending it to the end of the history on main as shown in the current tree history (at location J).